const cards = {
    0: {id: 1, question: "I keep dollaz on my head.", answer: "Gunna", difficulty: 'easy'},
    1: {id: 2, question: "Drip too hard, donâ€™t stand too close", answer: "Lil Baby", difficulty: 'easy'},
    2: {id: 3, question: "I'm Pushin' P, that's my favorite alphabet", answer: "Gunna", difficulty: 'easy'},
    3: {id: 4, question: "Momma moved to 85 North, not 85 South", answer: "Young Thug", difficulty: 'medium'},
    4: {id: 5, question: "Mo' money, mo' problems", answer: "Future", difficulty: 'medium'},
    5: {id: 6, question: "In New York I milly rock.", answer: "Playboi Carti", difficulty: 'medium'},
    6: {id: 7, question: "Anyways.", answer: "Young Nudy", difficulty: 'medium'},
    7: {id: 8, question: "My palms consistently itching", answer: "Gunna", difficulty: 'hard'},
    8: {id: 9, question: "Go and get some money, gotta get some money, never hold ya hand.", answer: "Young Nudy", difficulty: 'hard'},
    9: {id: 10, question: "Money sittin tall, Yao Ming", answer: "Playboi Carti", difficulty: 'hard'}
};

export default cards;